We built Ailurus for creators who want to own their audience and their payout path.
Centralized platforms take large cuts, control your files, and can remove you overnight.
Web3 alternatives ask fans for wallets, gas fees, and seed phrases — not mainstream ready.
Ailurus fixes this with Google login, USDC subscriptions, Walrus storage, and Seal paywalls.
Landing page — publish privately and get paid globally.
Scroll — creators keep USDC revenue; fans never see gas or WAL tokens.
Tap "View live demo" to enter the product on Sui Testnet.
Feed — browse posts from on-chain creators in a familiar social layout.
Not a wallet dashboard — it feels like Instagram or Threads.
Open Explore to discover creator profiles.
Discover creators registered through our Move contract on Sui.
Each profile shows price, posts, and subscriber-only encrypted drops.
Subscriber-only content stays locked until a fan pays in USDC.
Tap Subscribe — the Move contract records subscription state on chain.
USDC settles to the creator; Enoki sponsors all SUI gas fees.
Back to Feed — exclusive albums unlock instantly.
Seal decrypts media only for active subscribers.
Behind the UI: encrypted bytes live on Walrus; Seal enforces access policy.
Creators upload via Walrus SDK — Cetus swaps USDC to WAL for storage fees.
Our Cloudflare worker sponsors gas through Enoki with an allowlisted Move target list.
Identity, settlement, storage, and privacy — one product path on Sui Testnet.
In summary: Ailurus is a Web2-grade creator subscription layer on the full Sui stack.
Repo is public, contracts are live on Testnet, Mainnet target: July 2026.
Next: Enoki production config, creator onboarding, and analytics. Thank you.